

SHAH

UI / UX DESIGNER

Graphic Design

UI / UX Design

Front-End Dev

2D Animation

About me:

Experienced graphic designer with 11 years in the industry. Keenly interested in front-end development and UI / UX design. Known for a strong work ethic, passion for learning, and a drive for excellence in competitive environments.

Name Muhammad Shahril Fadzlyn

Bin Baharin

Language Malay • Native

English • Basic

CONTACT

Mobile 016 - 9191 002

E-mail shahrilfadzlyn@gmail.com

Website shahrilfadzlyn.github.io/portfolio

Address 11, Jalan Wangsa 1/3,

Taman Wangsa Permai, 52200, Kuala Lumpur

REFERENCE

Name Mr. S S Loong

Position Manager of Prepress Dept.

Mobile 017 - 692 1538

Address UPA PRESS SDN. BHD.

Lot 8228, Batu 6½, Jalan Kuchai Lama 58200 Kuala Lumpur.



WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 - Present UPA Press Sdn. Bhd.

Graphic Designer (Freelance)

Locum Net Asia Sdn. Bhd
Creative Designer (Freelance)

2021 - 2022 Jawi Streetwear

Founder / Product Designer (Self-employed)

2017 - 2018 SF Motion Studio

Founder / 2D Animator (Self-employed)

2014 - 2017 UPA Press Sdn. Bhd.

Graphic Designer (Permanent)

2013 - 2014 iProduksi

2D Animator (Freelance)

FNF Printing

Graphic Designer (Self-employed)

Vermilion Concept

Wedding Photographer (Self-employed)

2011 DotPerInchStudio

Graphic Designer (Internship)



EDUCATION

2011 - 2013 Ba (hons) Media Practice with Animation

Second Class Honours (Upper Division)

University of the West of England, United Kingdom

2008 - 2011 Diploma in Digital Media Design

CGPA 3.67

Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau

2006 - 2007 **SPM; 1A, 3B, 2C, 2D, 1E**

SMK Sri Tasik, Kuala Lumpur



ACHIEVEMENT

2015 Best Performance Award

UPA Press Sdn Bhd.

2014 Best Performance Award

UPA Press Sdn Bhd.

2010 **1st Place winner**, Graphic Design Technology,

Malaysia Skills Competition, 19th

Best Artwork Award, Digital Media, 5th Semester

Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau

All Rounder Best Artwork Award

Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau



TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Suite

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Flash/Animate, After Effects, Premiere & Audition

Microsoft Office Suite
Word, Excel & Powerpoint

Coding

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

Other Software/App

Figma, VSCode, Canva, Capcut, ChatGPT 4



MUHAMMAD SHAHRIL FADZLYN BIN BAHARIN

UI / UX DESIGNER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer

UPA Press Sdn. Bhd. 2017 - Present (Freelance) 2014 - 2017 (Permanent)

- Designed table calendars and diaries for domestic and international clients, adhering to their brand guidelines.
- Maintained clear communication with clients throughout the design process, finalizing artwork to their satisfaction.
- Utilized laser cutting and prepress printing machines to create color proofs and mock-up samples.
- Collaborated effectively with sales, supervisors, and production to ensure project success.
- Contributed to the development of new products through participation in the R&D team.
- Photographed product lines to create visually appealing marketing materials.
- · Mentored junior graphic designers.
- Contributed to UI/UX design for the company website & appusing Figma.

Creative Designer (Freelance)

Locum Net Asia Sdn. Bhd. | 2021 - Present

- Developed the company's branding (logo, business card, etc).
- Contributed to UI/UX design for the company website & app.
- Conceptualized and produced a video ad to promote the company's app.
- Designed the company's marketing materials.

Founder / Product Designer (Self-employed)

Jawi Streetwear | 2021 - 2022

- Developed brand identity (logo, marketing materials, etc).
- Conducted product research, designed & launched website & social media.
- Established relationships with key suppliers for cost-effective delivery.
- Generated engaging content (photos, videos) for multi-channel marketing.
- Developed customer relationships & drove sales.

Founder / 2D Animator (Self-employed)

SF Motion Studio | 2017 - 2018

- Created engaging 2D animation content for Facebook and YouTube.
- Freelanced as a 2D animator and graphic designer on Fiverr, serving international clients.

2D Animator (Freelance)

iProduksi | 2013 - 2014

 Developed concept art and produced animated projects, including a music video for a TV3 campaign and a cartoon series pilot episode.

Wedding photographer (Self-employed)

Vermilion Concept | 2013 - 2014

Captured wedding ceremony moments through professional photography.

Graphic Designer (Self-employed)

FNF Printing | 2013 - 2014

- Established our company's brand identity (logo, business cards, etc.).
- Designed marketing materials for clients, including bunting, banners, business cards, and T-shirts.